<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Animal Police Foundation on Animal Police Organization</title><link>https://allatrendorseg.github.io/en/</link><description>Recent content in Animal Police Foundation on Animal Police Organization</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://allatrendorseg.github.io/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About</title><link>https://allatrendorseg.github.io/en/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://allatrendorseg.github.io/en/about/</guid><description>People for Animals 2013 Foundation Our foundation is an organization of citizen volunteers that was founded in 2013. Our founding members have several years of animal rescue experience. For us, animal rescue is a vocation, and we do it voluntarily in our spare time.
Our foundation aims to help animals&amp;rsquo; well-being and quality of life and to immediately rescue animals that have fallen victim to animal cruelty by cooperating with the authorities.</description></item><item><title>Donate!</title><link>https://allatrendorseg.github.io/en/donate/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://allatrendorseg.github.io/en/donate/</guid><description>Donate Materials Contact us to get information of what we might need at the moment, as it could change with time.
Some donations we always take use of:
Cat food Cat litter Cat baskets / beds / blankets Donate Money Donations help us maintain the CatHouse, pay our veterinary bills, buy the necessary food and medicine for our animals.
If you would like to support our work, you can help with even the smallest amount.</description></item><item><title>Volunteering</title><link>https://allatrendorseg.github.io/en/help/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://allatrendorseg.github.io/en/help/</guid><description>How can you help?
CatHouse Our foundation&amp;rsquo;s CatHouse operates at the Pet Clinic in Buda, courtesy of Dr. Hacco Oren, so our cats are under direct medical supervision.
We operate with a constantly full house, we receive animals in distress from all over the country, for whom we are looking for responsible owners after their recovery and rehabilitation.
Our volunteers take care of the cats.
The home welcomes visitors and volunteers by prior arrangement.</description></item><item><title>Contact</title><link>https://allatrendorseg.github.io/en/contact/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://allatrendorseg.github.io/en/contact/</guid><description>Contact Write an email to us:
Email: info@allatrendorseg.com
Or send a message directly from this page:
Your Name Email Address An email address is required. Message</description></item><item><title>Yearly Reports</title><link>https://allatrendorseg.github.io/en/report/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://allatrendorseg.github.io/en/report/</guid><description>2022
2021
2020
2019
2018
2017</description></item></channel></rss>